准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
美人鱼战士
和企鹅男孩
导演
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜总监
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
客串
配音 美人鱼战士
配音 企鹅男孩
配音 射线恶魔
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的全新冒险
The new adventures of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
一起加入裤头村最崇高最勇猛
We join Bikini Bottom's noblest, boldest
最老的超级英雄
oldest superheroes
看他们英勇地准备度假
as they bravely prepare for vacation
叠
装
可是等等
But wait
我们的英雄到度假村放松期间
While our heroes relax at Leisure Village
谁来帮美人鱼基地看家
who will watch the Mermalair?
海绵战士
ManSponge
和海星男孩
And BoyPatrick
前来报到
Reporting for duty
好好好  跟我来
Yeah, yeah, follow me
准备起飞
Up, up and away
邪恶
Evil
我们想要你们两个
Now, we want you boys
看好这个地方
to keep an eye on the place
帮绿植浇水  并且确保
Water the plants and make sure
我的天啊  派大星
Oh, my gosh, Patrick
这是我见过最棒的超英秘密道具墙
This is the greatest wall
of superhero secret gadgetry ever
我要玩宇宙射线
I'm gonna play with the Cosmic Ray
我去拿海底手套
I get the Aquaglove
你们给我慢着
Hold on there, boys
这种东西不能随便乱玩
You cannot play with this stuff
那昏沉之球呢
What about the Orb of Confusion?
不行
No, no
长时间暴露在昏沉之球附近
Prolonged exposure to the Orb of Confusion
会导致你们昏昏沉沉
will give you confusion
那无影船呢
What about the Invisible Boatmobile?
无影船最不能乱动
Especially not the Invisible Boatmobile
我们说  什么都不准动
When we say, "Don't touch anything"
就是要表示  什么都不准动
we mean, "Don't touch anything"
明不明白
Do you understand?
清楚明白  靠谱小跟班企鹅男孩
Loud and clear, trusted boy companion
很好
Great
钥匙拿去
Here are the keys
一周后再见
We'll see you in a week
准备起飞
Up, up and away
海星男孩快来
Come, BoyPatrick
英雄走了  就得靠我们来驱逐邪恶
While our heroes are away, we will keep evil at bay
射射射
Ma-ma-ma-
怎么了  靠谱小跟班
What is it, trusted sidekick?
射射射
Ma-ma-ma-
射线恶魔
Man Ray
海绵宝宝  他怎么不来追我们
Hey, SpongeBob, how come he's not chasing us?
他貌似被冻住了
Looks like he's frozen or something
冻冻冻
Fr-fr-fr
fro-fro-fro
估计是某种牢房
It appears to be some sort of prison chamber
还是用冷冻塔塔酱做的
made out of frozen tartar sauce
不可思议
This is incredible
肮脏泡泡第一
Next to the Dirty Bubble
射线恶魔是美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩的
the evil Man Ray is the all-time greatest arch-nemesis
第二大死对头
of Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
我有好多问题想问他
I have so many questions to ask him
冰冻
解冻
派大星  你在干什么
Pat, what are you doing?
我们什么都不能乱动
We're not supposed to touch anything
可你说你有问题要问
But you said you had a question
我们会有危险的
We could get in trouble
他都说了不能乱动
He said not to touch anything
冰冻
解冻
一样也不能乱解冻超级坏蛋
And that includes unfreezing a supervillain
我自由了
I'm free
其实  射线
Actually Mr. uh
恶魔先生
Man Ray, sir
只有你头自由了
only your head is free
赐予我至高无上的邪恶特权
By the supreme authority of wickedness
我  射线恶魔
I, the evil Man Ray
命令你们释放我
command you to release me
立刻脱离这座冰冻牢房
from this frozen prison at once
那个
Well, uh
射线恶魔先生
Mr. evil Man Ray, sir
我们不能那样
we can't do that
为什么
Why not?
因为你很坏
Because you're evil
意思是说  如果我是好人
You mean, if I was good
那就会放我走了
then you'd let me go?
对  那当然了
Yeah, sure, why not?
那么
Then, uh
这样的话  我是好人
in that case, I am good
真的吗
Really?
对  真的
Yes, really
真的真的吗
Really, really?
对对
Yes, yes
真的真的
really, really
真的真的真的吗
Really, really, really?
对对对  差不多得了
Yes, yes, already
我是好人  我是好人
I'm good, I'm good
还不快放我走
Now let me out of here
否则后果自负
or you'll suffer dire consequences
那样也差不多
Well, that's good enough for me
冰冻
解冻
两个白痴
You fools
准备好被我消灭吧
Prepare to be eradicated
我是怎么了
What's wrong with me?
这可恶的装置是什么
What is this infernal contraption?
别装傻了  射线恶魔
Don't play dumb, Man Ray--
你应该知道这是痒痒腰带
you know that's the Tickle Belt
美人鱼战士在第17集就对你用过了
Mermaidman used on you in episode number 17
痒痒腰带
跟第17集一个样
我爱看那集
I love that episode
我也是
Me, too
戴着这腰带肯定逃不走
I'll never get out of here wearing this belt
我需要一个邪恶计划
I need an evil plan
骗他们两个把腰带摘下来
that will trick them to take it off me
表演课该派上用场了
Time for those acting lessons to pay off
还记得美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩那时
Remember that part when Mermaidman and Barnacle--
哭啊
Sob
泣啊
Cry
我好苦
Woe is me
你们不知道
You don't know
当坏蛋这么久会有何感想
what it's like being evil for so long
我好想当
How I wish to be
好人
good
要是能有几个好英雄
If only some kind heroes
可以带我踏入正轨就好了
would show me the path to decency
我们可以教你当好人
We could teach you how to be good
然后就可以放你走了
and then we'll let you go
那就太好了
That would be fantastic
我要假装到底
I'll fake my way through this
就跟上中学那会一个样
just like I did in high school
好了  射线恶魔
Okay, Man Ray
准备好入学好人学校了吗
are you ready for your first day at goodness school?
派大星  拿钱包
Pat, get your wallet out
好的  好人第一课
Okay, goodness lesson number one
看到有人掉了钱包
You see someone drop their wallet
派大星  钱包扔地上
Patrick, drop the wallet
现在  你会怎么做
Now, what would you do?
不好意思  先生
Excuse me, sir
你钱包好像掉了
but I do believe you've dropped your wallet
看着不像我的
Doesn't look familiar to me
什么
What?
我都看到是你掉的了
I just saw you drop it--
给
here
才不是我的
Nope, it's not mine
就是你的
It is yours
我
I
我要当个大好人
I'm trying to be a good person
把钱包还给你
and return it to you
把什么还给谁
Return what to who?
你不是
Aren't you
裤头村身份证
不是驾照
派大星
派大星吗
Patrick Star?
是
Yup
这是你的身份证
And this is your ID?
对
Yup
我发现了这张身份证
I found this ID
放在你钱包里
in this wallet
这样的话
and if that's the case
钱包一定就是你的了
this must be your wallet
听起来挺有道理
That makes sense to me
那就收下吧
Then take it
这不是我钱包
It's not my wallet
你个死脑筋
You dim bulb
把钱包收好  不然我就扒了你胳膊
Take back your wallet or I'll rip your arms off
错了
Wrong
好人不会
Good people don't
扒下别人的胳膊
rip other people's arms off
停
Stop
好的  好人第二课
Okay, goodness lesson number two
看到有人费劲地搬运一个重包裹
You see someone struggling with a heavy package
你会怎么做
What do you do?
你好  朋友
Hello, friend
我注意到你在费尽气力搬运那个包裹
I noticed you were struggling with that package
需要我帮忙吗
Would you like some help?
抱歉  我能重来吗
Sorry, can I start over?
我注意到你
I noticed you were
又得重来了
Got to start again
你个笨手笨脚的粉东西
You butter-fingered pink thing
箱子里的到底是什么
What's in that box, anyhow?
我一大堆的钱包
My wallets
海绵宝宝  挠他痒痒
Oh, SpongeBob, tickle him
痒死了
That tickles
不过值得
but it's worth it
好的  好人第三课
All right, goodness lesson number three
我想想
let's see
有了
I've got one
我在想一个1到100之间的数
I'm thinking of a number between one and 100
这个数是多少
What is it?
错
Wrong
住手  住手
Stop, stop
派大星
Hey, Patrick
当好人跟猜数没关系
that's not about being good
快放手  海绵宝宝
Let go of it, SpongeBob
派大星  只有他做坏事了才能用
Pat, we can use it only when he's bad
放手
Let go
不  你放手
No, you let go
放手
Let go
频率上升
Frequency rising
腰带失控了
belt out of control
连DNA都痒了
Tickling my DNA
快停下吧
Make it stop
请你们了
Please
听到了吗  派大星
Did you hear that, Patrick?
他刚才说了请
He said the "p" word
琴
Peanuts?
不对  是请
No, "please"
那样也差不多
Well, that's good enough for me
他应该重组了
I guess he's reconstituted
那叫改过自新
Rehabilitated
康       复
那就祝你健康
Gesundheit
今天你毕业了  射线恶魔
It's graduation day, Man Ray
这是通往你未来的钥匙
This is the key to your future
看看他  派大星
Just look at him, Patrick
大好人的典范
the picture of goodness
不可以动那个
We're not supposed to touch that stuff
那个也不能动
We're not supposed to touch that, either
真的不能乱动那些东西  先生
We are really not supposed to touch those, sir
好人用不上武器  就比如
Good people have no use for weapons such as
我唯一好的专长  就是作恶
The only thing I'm good at is being evil
再见了  白痴
So long, suckers
那什么味道  海绵宝宝
What's that smell, SpongeBob?
那个  派大星
That, Patrick
是失败的味道
is the smell of defeat
好  我还以为是我皮肤的味道
Good, I thought it was my skin
别管你皮肤了  派大星
Forget about your skin, Patrick
射线恶魔还是坏蛋
Man Ray is still bad
得有人出手阻止他
and someone has to stop him
这项重责大任
This is a job
要交给美人鱼战士
for Mermaidman
和企鹅男孩
And Barnacleboy
前往无影船
To the Invisible Boatmobile
点火
Ignition on
等等
Wait--
我没驾照
I don't have a license
这可是艘无影船对吧
Well, this is an invisible boat, right?
那你就需要无影的驾照
So you need an invisible license
你是我最棒的小跟班了  企鹅男孩
You're the best sidekick ever, Barnacleboy
谢天谢地有无影安全带
Thank goodness for invisible seat belts
给我让开  傻子
Out of my way, fools
你们再也控制不了我了
You no longer have control of me
现在这里属于射线恶魔
and now this town belongs to Man Ray
别得意得太早  大坏蛋
Not so fast, arch villain
我们还有昏沉之球
We still have the Orb of Confusion
接招
Take this
不费吹灰之力
Well, that was easy
第一航海银行
好了  所有人
All right, people
全都不许动
Everybody stand right where you are
我要你们
I want you to, uh
不行  不准笑
No, no, stop giggling
不然我就
or I'll have to
不准笑  白痴
Stop laughing, you fools
需要办什么业务  先生
What can I do for you, sir?
我来告诉你要做什么
I'll tell you what you can do
给我你们的
Give me all of your, uh
给我
Give me
给我你们的
give me all of your
给我
Give me
腰带没了
The belt is gone
可我还是觉得痒
but I still feel its tickle
做坏事的冲动都没了
The urge to do bad is gone
我还是开个活期存款账户好了
I guess I'll just open a checking account
开
关
射线恶魔
Man Ray
你别怕  海绵宝宝
No need to be alarmed, SpongeBob
你教我的好人课让我洗心革面了
Your teachings have transformed me
并且
Besides
我还开了印着小狗狗的支票
I have checks with little poodles on them
射线恶魔
这个我再也用不着了
I won't be needing this anymore
再见  好人朋友
Farewell, fellow do-gooder
再见  射线恶魔
Bye, Man Ray
我们成功了
We did it
跟美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩一个样
just like the real Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
我们拯救世界了
We saved the day
是不是不可思议  派大星
Isn't it incredible, Patrick?
派大星
Patrick?
派大星  你应该知道这个已经关了吧
Patrick, you know that thing's turned off, right?
派大星
Patrick
Patrick?
松鼠玩笑
翻译: 1440kHz
导演
分镜总监
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
喜剧王
好了  请各位就座
Okay, everybody settle down
欢迎光临喜剧王
Welcome to the Komedy Krab
请大家热烈欢迎
Now, please give a warm welcome
我们第一位喜剧演员
to our first comic
存在感低的杜奇威廉姆斯
the indiscernible Doogie Williams
各位观众晚上好
Good evening, folks
直接跳过笑话
I'm going to skip the jokes
开始朝你们扔派
and get right to the part where I throw pies at you
希望我表现能跟他一样好
I hope I do as good as that guy
天啊  观众看什么都笑得出来
Man, those people will laugh at anything
别紧张  小子
Don't sweat it, kid
我帮你暖场了
I got 'em all warmed up for you
各位鳍声有请海绵宝宝
Put your fins together for SpongeBob SquarePants
加油  海绵宝宝
Go get 'em, SpongeBob
女士们水母们
Ladies and jellyfish
大家先前有注意过盐瓶吗
have you ever noticed salt shakers?
就是  每天晚上打烊都要装满
I mean, you fill them up every night at closing
就是说  都上哪去了
and, I mean, where does it all go?
都明白我意思吧
You know what I mean?
还有番茄
And tomatoes--
那些玩意是怎么回事
what's the deal on those things?
因为  就是要切成片
Because, I mean you chop them up into slices
可
but
番茄到底算蔬菜还是
What are they, vegetables or
水果
fruit?
怎么就能做番茄酱了呢
And what does that make ketchup?
烦死了
Oh, brother
这位太烂了
This guy stinks
讲笑话的
Funny guy
送你个玩笑
I got a joke for you
什么东西又臭
What smells rotten
又让人犯困
and puts people to sleep?
毒气
Noxious gas?
错
No
你的表演
Your act
你们有没有注意到
Did you ever notice
那个
how, uh
叉子
forks, uh
叉子吗
Forks?
搞什么
Come on
快啊  海绵宝宝
Quick, SpongeBob
找个幽默的东西讲
Make a witty observation
恶心
PU
你们有没有注意到
Did you ever notice
松鼠的牙齿有多大吗
how big squirrels' teeth are?
确实
That's true
就是
I mean
完全都能在上面停飞机了
you could land a plane on those things
还有松鼠毛是怎么回事
And what's up with that squirrel fur?
看来跳蚤也得有家住
I guess fleas need a home, too
松鼠毛
Squirrel fur
还挺臭的
And they smell
不过  大家一样也会臭
but hey, you'd stink, too
条件是三个月全埋土里
if you spent three months buried in dirt
为什么必须要不止一只的松鼠
Why does it take more than one squirrel
才能换灯泡呢
to change a light bulb?
为什么
Why?
因为松鼠傻得要命
Because they're so darn stupid
也太好笑了吧  珊迪
That's a good one, eh, Sandy?
对
Y-yeah
实在是出神入化  小子
That was fantastic, boy
观众全都笑翻了
You really knocked them out
改天再办一次笑话之夜
I think I'll do this joke night again
就由你来当主演
with you as the headliner
没想到我会当上主演
I never thought I could be a headliner
不管那是啥
Whatever that is
主演就是
The headliner's the one
可以表演过后赚钱加打扫的人
who cleans up after the show
最起码不是让我好自为之
Well, at least I don't have to clean up my act
只讲松鼠玩笑就好  小子
Stick with the squirrel jokes, boy
动作快
Now get busy
拖拖拖
Mops, mops, mops
那些玩意怎么回事
What's up with those things?
我说真的
I mean, really
珊迪
Hey, Sandy
你好  海绵宝宝
Howdy, SpongeBob
刚刚的表演你喜欢吗
Did you like the show?
其实吧  海绵宝宝
Well, a-actually, SpongeBob
不喜欢
no
那些玩笑很伤人  你心里也清楚
Those jokes are hurtful and you know it
没什么的  珊迪
Come on, Sandy
单纯开个玩笑而已
I was just joking
就是说  众所周知
I mean everybody knows
你就是全裤头村最聪明的
you're the smartest one at Bikini Bottom
这我无法反驳
Well, I can't argue with that
我们都会偶尔自嘲一下
We all gotta laugh at ourselves once in a while
我一直都自嘲
I do it all the time
你说得对  海绵宝宝
You're right, SpongeBob
我确实有点敏感了
I was being a little too sensitive
别见怪
No hard feelings
便宜货超市
好的  除臭剂
Okay, deodorant
来看看
Let's see
买滚珠还是买膏状
Roll-on or stick?
她得两个都买
I think she should buy both
大家快来看
Look, guys
是那只笨松鼠
It's the stupid squirrel
有了
I know--
大家一起来试着跟它交流吧
let's try and communicate with it
你好  小家伙
Hello, little critter
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
别靠近松鼠  比利
Don't stand too close to a squirrel, Billy
会被传染傻的
You'll catch its stupid
好的  妈
Okay, Mom
愚蠢不是病毒
Stupidity isn't a virus
但传染力堪比病毒
but it sure is spreading like one
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
松鼠松鼠
Squirrely, squirrely
松松鼠
squirrely, squirrel
因为它们就是傻
Because they're stupid
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
嗨  珊迪
Hi, Sandy
我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you
那些松鼠玩笑的事
about them squirrel jokes
早就谈过了  记得吗
We already talked about that, remember?
海绵宝宝  事情很严重
SpongeBob, this is serious
你一直给大家开松鼠玩笑
Since you've been telling them jokes
现在大家都区别对待我
people have been treating me different
海绵宝宝  占用五分钟
SpongeBob, five minutes
你好  珊迪
Hel-lo, Sandy
我是派大星
Me Patrick
你明不明白
Do you un-der-stand?
松鼠啊
Squirrels
看见没
Y-y-you see?
这就是我想跟你说的
That's what I'm talking about
派大星是那样的
That's just Patrick
到处卖傻
He's fooling around
身为你朋友  我要你
I'm just asking you as a friend
别再讲松鼠玩笑了  好吗
please lay off them squirrel jokes, okay?
向台下观众讲点别的玩笑话
Tell some of them other jokes you got
别的玩笑话
Other jokes?
我有不少呢
I got a million of them
谢了  海绵宝宝
Thanks, SpongeBob
你果然还是能理解
I knew you'd understand
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
各位鳍声有请海绵宝宝
Put your fins together for SpongeBob SquarePants
嗨
Hi
大家听过破产金鱼的事吗
Did you hear about the goldfish who went bankrupt?
现在金鱼变铜鱼了
Now he's a bronze fish
什么
What?
他说什么
What did he say?
大家应该都听过了
I guess you heard that one
我没听过
I haven't heard it
很好笑的  海绵宝宝
Good one, SpongeBob
谢谢  你真是心善
Thank you, you're too kind
这水怎么说
What about this water?
就是  这玩意到处都是
I mean, the stuff's everywhere
再讲个松鼠跟灯泡的笑话吧
Tell the one about the squirrel and the light bulbs
这个怎么说
What about this thing?
再讲点松鼠玩笑
Get on with the squirrel jokes
松鼠玩笑
Squirrel jokes
该怎么办
What do I do?
海绵宝宝  你要做出选择
SpongeBob, you've got a choice to make
选朋友  还是选事业
Your friends or your career?
松鼠玩笑
Squirrel jokes
大家好
Howdy, y'all
为什么必须要不止一只的松鼠
How come it takes more than one squirrel
才能装灯泡呢
to screw in a light bulb?
因为松鼠就是傻得要命
Because they're so darn stupid
我的粉丝
My people
说真的  各位
Seriously, folks
我特别想感谢我的朋友  珊迪
I want to give a special thanks to my friend Sandy
珊迪  看不出来吗
Sandy, don't you see?
观众很爱我开的那些玩笑
The crowd loves these jokes
你们说对不
Am I right?
看不出来吗  珊迪
Don't you see, Sandy?
我们是在跟你欢笑
We're laughing with you
不是对你嘲笑
not at you
能理解我了不  珊迪
Do you understand now, Sandy?
能不
Do you?
我很理解现在的情况  海绵宝宝
I understand exactly what's going on, SpongeBob
很好
Great
我就知道你迟早会明白
I knew sooner or later you'd understand
真是宽宏大量
What a great sport
大家一起为珊迪鼓掌
Let's give a big hand to Sandy
不过鼓掌鼓慢点  因为可别忘了
But clap slow, because remember
她是只松鼠
she's a squirrel
谢谢
Thank you
大家都是好观众  然后就
You've been a wonderful audience and, uh
晚安了
good night
又一场精彩的表演  海绵宝宝
Another spectacular performance, SpongeBob
这是什么  粉丝来信
What's this, a fan letter?
你说的对
海绵宝宝
玩笑真好笑
明天来树屋
好好庆祝庆祝
珊迪
你成功了  海绵宝宝
You did it, SpongeBob
既保住了事业  又保住了朋友
You get to keep your career and your friends
我很高兴
I'm glad that
珊迪总算能看到我的喜剧才能了
Sandy can finally see the genius of my comedy
早安  珊迪
Good morning, Sandy
你好啊
Well, how-dee
珊迪  你没事吧
Sandy, are you feeling all right?
我只是在发扬我的松鼠天性
I'm just being my au-naturally squirrely self
请进吧
Well, come on in
你一定累坏了
Y'all must be tired
给大家讲了好多笑话
from telling them funny jokes all the time
不然你就休息一下好不好
Why don't you take a load off?
珊迪  这座椅好像有点不对劲
Sandy, I think something's wrong with this seat
才没有  我只是涂了点胶水上去
Naw, I just done put glue on it
胶水
这样你才不会摔下来
so you wouldn't fall off
这些花是送我的吗
Are them flowers for me?
居然还带了个花瓶
You even done got me a vase
可是珊迪  那
But Sandy, that
那不是
that's not a
也太飘亮了吧
Ain't that purdy?
珊迪  我需要水
Sandy, I need wa
你说得对
That's right
你是海底生物
You's a sea critter
海底生物需要什么东西来着呢
Now, what was that thing sea critters need?
我想想
Let's see
海底生物需要
sea critters need, uh
水
Wa
等等
Wait
先别提醒我
Don't tell me
我好像知道
I know this one
水
Wa
钱包
Wallet?
手表
Watch?
华夫饼
Waffles?
珊迪
Sandy
水
Water
那你怎么不早点说
Well, why didn't you just say so?
这就给你
Here you go
没错  我们松鼠确实傻
Yup, us squirrels sure is stupid
珊迪
Sandy
松鼠就是笨
Squirrels is dumb
珊迪
Sandy
好了珊迪  我都理解了
Okay, Sandy, I get it
你说什么
What's that?
还要吗
You want more?
好啊
Okey-dokey
给海底生物多来点水
More water for the sea critter
行了  珊迪
Okay, Sandy
行了
okay
我都理解了
I get it
不开松鼠玩笑了
No more squirrel jokes
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
谢谢  非常谢谢大家
Thank you, thank you very much
我来的路上撞见了一只松鼠
On my way over here I ran into a squirrel
我就说  喂
and I said, "Hey
怎么不找几个松鼠朋友过来
"why don't you go get a couple squirrel friends
一起去换个灯泡呢
and we'll go change a light bulb?"
不过说真的  各位
But seriously, folks
唯一会比松鼠还傻的东西
the only thing dumber than a squirrel
就是海绵
is a sponge
我们海绵傻到
I mean, we're so dumb
连脊椎都没有
we don't even have a vertebrae
快看我
Look at me
我没骨头
I got no bones
确实
That's true
螃蟹
Crabs?
烦死了
Oh, brother
小气到都不愿意花费注意力了
They're so cheap they can't even pay attention
确实
It's true
我很小气
I am cheap
来说说鱼的事情
Now let me tell you about those fish
实在是臭死了
Boy, are they smelly
怎么会有生物
How could a creature
天天泡水  味道还这么臭
who spends so much time in the water smell so bad?
我说真的
I mean, really
肥皂  肥皂
Soap, soap
什么是肥皂
what is soap?
更别提海星了
And don't even get me started on starfish